hdicon.com 2011-03-13

# Privacy policy | HD icon - Resources for web designers

#### Revised November 4, 2009

At HDicon, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitor’s will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties unless by governmental order.

##### What are cookies?

All browsers offer “cookies” and if you permit their use, they will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site that placed the cookie. A cookie is a small text file. It is not a program, or a plug-in. It could not be used as a virus, and it cannot access your hard drive. Cookies simply assist in tracking which features you like the most and allow content to be customized upon your return, according to prior preferences at that site. They would not gather or hold any personal information.

At HDicon, we may use cookies to store your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites.

HDicon will **NOT** :

  * Use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information.
  * Have cookies that contain any personally identifiable information about you.
  * Merge or associate our cookie information with any other visitor’s confidential and identifiable data obtained by us or from 3rd parties. 

You also have flexible choices in respect to cookies. By simply modifying your browser preferences, you have the right to choose whether to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. For more information on how to modify your browser settings in order to block or filter cookies, please visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/>

However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the web may not be complete. Some sites require cookies to function, such as those with e-commerce features. In addition, if you disable cookies, you will not be eligible to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us or other Internet sites.

##### Registration Forms

Our site’s registration form requires users to provide information, such as their name, email. This information is only used to get in touch with the customer when necessary and is never sold or shared.

##### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. HDicon is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the websites you visit once you have left our site. We only link to general audience sites but cannot be responsible for any redirection or content changes over which we have no control. Please contact us immediately if there is a problem with any of our links.

##### Contact the website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or concerns about this website, please contact: [webmaster@hdicon.com](mailto:webmaster@hdicon.com)

##### Your consent to this agreement

By using the HDicon, you consent to the collection and use of information by HDicon as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

##### Copyright

If you are a copyright owner, or are authorized to act on behalf of an owner of the copyright or of any exclusive right under the copyright, and believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please report your notice of infringement to HDicon by providing all the necessary information to [webmaster@hdicon.com](mailto:\('webmaster@hdicon.com'\))
